Nancy Sweezy collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 7: Spirited Objects and OXYGEN Media Project, 1996-2001, Bulk: 1998-2001
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Interview notes and photos: Kim Ellington (Vale, North Carolina), 1998, 14 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/11)
    - Interview notes and photos: Hewell's Pottery (Gillsville, Georgia), 1998, 11 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/12)
    - Interview notes and photos: Mark Hewitt - Piedmont Potter (Pittsboro, North Carolina), 1998, 23 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 73/13)
    - Mark Hewitt: Potter (North Carolina State exhibit book), 1997 (Box-folder 89/7)
    - Interview notes and photos: Billy Ray Hussey, 1998 (Box-folder 74/1)
    - Interview notes and photos: Charles Lisk and others, 1998 (Box-folder 74/2)
    - Owens interview transcripts for Spirited Objects, 1998 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - Notes and photos from Spirited Objects project interviews: Joe Reinhardt (Vale, North Carolina), 1998, 6 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 74/4)
    - Fieldwork - North Carolina, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 74/5-6)
    - Fieldwork - North Carolina, 2001 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - Spirited Objects interviews in Canon County, Tennessee, 1998 (Box-folder 74/8-9)
    - Spirited Objects - Canon County, Tennessee, information, 1998 (Box-folder 74/10)
    - Spirited Objects - baskets from South Carolina, Tennessee, California, undated, 2 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 74/11)
    - Spirited Objects - blacksmiths from Connecticut, 1998 (Box-folder 74/12)
    - Spirited Objects - blacksmiths from Massachusetts, 1998 (Box-folder 74/13)
    - Spirited Objects - blacksmiths of New England, 1998 (Box-folder 74/14)
    - Spirited Objects - blacksmiths of New Hampshire, 1998, 3 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 74/15)
    - Spirited Objects - Charleston baskets, 1998 (Box-folder 75/1)
    - Spirited Objects - Cowboy crafts, Indian carving, Eskimo parkas, undated (Box-folder 75/2)
    - Spirited Objects - decorative ironworkers, undated, 10 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 75/3)
    - Spirited Objects - Hispanic weaving and santos carving from New Mexico, undated (Box-folder 75/4)
    - Spirited Objects - Japanese-American and Chinese-American woodworking, 1998 (Box-folder 75/5)
    - Spirited Objects - Japanese-American and Chinese-American woodworking, 1998 (Box-folder 75/6)
    - Spirited Objects - Native American contacts, undated (Box-folder 75/7)
    - Spirited Objects - Pueblo pottery from New Mexico (xeroxed images), undated (Box-folder 75/8)
    - Spirited Objects - quilts of New England, 1998 (Box-folder 75/9)
    - Spirited Objects - quilts form California, Hawaii, New England, undated, 5 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 75/10)
    - Spirited Objects - possible designer/coordinator, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 75/11)
    - Spirited Objects - craft printed materials, 1998 (Box-folder 75/12)
    - Spirited Objects - publications, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 75/13)
    - Spirited Objects - budgets, 1998 (Box-folder 75/14)
    - Spirited Objects - fundraising, 1998 (Box-folder 75/15)
    - Spirited Objects - correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 75/16)
    - Spirited Objects - crafts people information, undated, 7 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 76/1)
    - Spirited Objects - possible exhibition categories, 1998 (Box-folder 76/2)
    - Spirited Objects - exhibit proposal, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - Spirited Objects - Renwick and museums, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - Spirited Objects - SITES, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - Spirited Objects - post-SITES and blow-up, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 76/6)
    - Spirited Objects - transition, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 76/7-10)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media, 2000-2001, 4 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 76/11)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media - masks, lace, dolls, quilts, others, 2000 (Box-folder 76/12)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media - quilts, 2000-2001, 9 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 77/1)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media - regalia, 2000-2001, 3 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 77/2)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media - correspondence with Kit Laybourne, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 77/3)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media - weaving, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 77/4)
    - Textiles project with Oxygen Media - Lists of contacts and artists, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 77/5)
    - NCMA and George, 1999, afc2017001_cf17; text files; original media: zip disk
    - Southern potters notes, 1998-1999, afc2017001_cf21; text files; original media: zip disk
    - Spirited Objects Business and related files, 1997-1999, afc2017001_cf21; text files; original media: zip disk
    - Spirited Objects files, 1999-2000, afc2017001_cf17; text files; original media: zip disk
    - Oxygen files, 2000, afc2017001_cf18; text files; original media: zip disk
    - North Carolina Museum of Art exhibition, 2001-2003, afc2017001_cf23; text files; original media: zip disk
    - North Carolina Museum of Art exhibition, 2002-2005, afc2017001_cf07; text files; original media: CD-ROM
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Spirited Objects/TAC, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph09_055 to ph09_058 (Box 21-22)
    - US tradition crafts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph09_059 to ph09_086 (Box 21-22)
    - Unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph09_087 to ph09_094 (Box 21-22)
    - Ben Owen III, 1997, AFC 2017/001: ph09_115 to ph09_133 (Box 21-22)
    - Oxygen quilts: Margaret Wood (Native American) and Ruth Ward, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_001 to ph19_020 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: Ed J. Miller, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_021 to ph19_036 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: MS Crossroads / Hystercine Rankin and Gustina Atlas, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_037 to ph19_053 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: MS Crossroads / Geraldine Nash and children, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_054 to ph19_073 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: Pat Hubbard, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_074 to ph19_087 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: textiles Connecticut and Louisiana, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_088 to ph19_103 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: Yvonne Wells, Bettye Kimbrell, and Mabel Murphy, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_104 to ph19_137 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen: Southeast Asian textiles, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_138 to ph19_152 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen quilts: Eli Leon collection, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_153 to ph19_184 (Box 40-42)
    - Oxygen weaving: NCGC, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_185 to ph19_192 (Box 40-42)
    - Spirited Objects baskets, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_193 to ph19_200 (Box 40-42)
    - Spirited Objects Wisconsin crafts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_201 to ph19_210 (Box 40-42)
    - Banjos and Canoes/ Henri Vaillencourt, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_211 to ph19_225 (Box 40-42)
    - Spirited Objects quilts: Rosie Lee Tompkins, Arbie Williams, Wanda Jones, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_226 to ph19_238 (Box 40-42)
    - New Mexico textiles, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_239 to ph19_257 (Box 40-42)
    - Southeast and California baskets, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_258 to ph19_266 (Box 40-42)
    - Alaska and Northwest coast, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_267 to ph19_284 (Box 40-42)
    - Cowboy Great Basin, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_285 to ph19_298 (Box 40-42)
    - North Carolina pottery - Ben Owen, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_299 to ph19_319 (Box 40-42)
    - Southwest pottery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_320 to ph19_337 (Box 40-42)
    - Dick Sexstone - metalwork, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_338 to ph19_349 (Box 40-42)
    - Walter Scadden - iron, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_350 to ph19_360 (Box 40-42)
    - Douglas Wilson - iron, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph19_361 to ph19_375 (Box 40-42)
    - Southwest pottery, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph20_001 to ph20_101 (Box 42-43)
    - Mark Hewitt Pottery - Pittsboro, North Carolina, 1998, AFC 2017/001: ph20_102 to ph20_152 (Box 42-43)
    - Kim Ellington - Vale, North Carolina, 1998, AFC 2017/001: ph20_153 to ph20_197 (Box 42-43)
    - Burlon Craig - Vale, North Carolina, 1998, AFC 2017/001: ph20_198 to ph20_234 (Box 42-43)
    - Louis Goings - Cherokee Basketry, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph20_235 to ph20_355 (Box 42-43)
    - Laverne Brackens slides - quilts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph22_001 to ph22_048 (Box 43-44)
    - Laverne Brackens slides - unlabeled, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph22_049 to ph22_054 (Box 43-44)
    - Quilts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph23_001 to ph23_005 (Box 44)
    - Textile weaving, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph23_006 to ph23_031 (Box 44)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - Walter blacksmith, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV06; 1 videotape
    - Billy Ray Hussey, 1998-04-22, AFC 2017/001: SR076; 1 audio cassette
    - Ben Owen at his pottery; Seagrove, North Carolina, 1998-04-26, AFC 2017/001: SR077; 1 audio cassette
    - Joe Reinhardt and Charles Lisk, 1998-04-28, AFC 2017/001: SR078; 1 audio cassette
    - Vernon Owens and Pam Owens; Jugtown Pottery, 1998-04, AFC 2017/001: SR079; 1 audio cassette
    - Cont. Vernon Owens and Pam Owens; Jugtown Pottery, 1998-04, AFC 2017/001: SR080; 1 audio cassette
    - Davy Arch; Cherokee, North Carolina, 1997-05-30, AFC 2017/001: SR081; 1 audio cassette
    - Mark Hewitt on pottery; Pittsboro, North Carolina, 1998-04-22, AFC 2017/001: SR082; 1 audio cassette
    - Kim Ellington; Vale, North Carolina, 1998-04-28, AFC 2017/001: SR083; 1 audio cassette
    - Mary Farrell and Dave Farrell on pottery; Seagrove, North Carolina, 1998-04, AFC 2017/001: SR084; 1 audio cassette
    - Vernon Owens; Jugtown Pottery, 1998-04, AFC 2017/001: SR085; 1 audio cassette
    - Trevor Wood on wood baskets, 1998-08-12, AFC 2017/001: SR086; 1 audio cassette
    - Trevor Wood - basketmaker; Murfreesboro, Tennessee, 1998-08-12, AFC 2017/001: SR087; 1 audio cassette
    - Mary and N. Davis; Tennessee, 1998-08-12, AFC 2017/001: SR088; 1 audio cassette
    - Mary Davis; Woodbury, Tennessee, 1998-08-12, AFC 2017/001: SR089; 1 audio cassette
    - Cont. Mary Davis; Woodbury, Tennessee, 1998-08-12, AFC 2017/001: SR090; 1 audio cassette
    - Josie Jones on basketmaking; Tennessee, 1998-08-13, AFC 2017/001: SR091; 1 audio cassette
    - "Gertie" Youngblood; Woodbury, Tennessee, 1998-08-13, AFC 2017/001: SR092; 1 audio cassette
    - Albert Thomas; Woodbury, Tennessee, 1998-08-13, AFC 2017/001: SR093; 1 audio cassette
    - Viella Estes on basketmaking; Tennessee, 1998-08-14, AFC 2017/001: SR094; 1 audio cassette
    - Viella Estes and family of basketmakers, Betty Tanner; Tennessee, 1998-08-14, AFC 2017/001: SR095; 1 audio cassette
    - Ida Pearl Davis and Thelma Hibdon, 1998-08-14, AFC 2017/001: SR096; 1 audio cassette
    - Ida Pearl Davis and Thelma Hibdon, 1998-08-14, AFC 2017/001: SR097; 1 audio cassette
    - George Martell on blacksmithing; Seekonk, Massachusetts, 1998-09-09, AFC 2017/001: SR098; 1 audio cassette
    - Leigh Momell on blacksmithing; Brattleboro, Vermont, 1991-09-15, AFC 2017/001: SR099; 1 audio cassette
    - Dimitri Gorakaris on blacksmithing; North Canaan, New Hampshire, 1998-09-15, AFC 2017/001: SR100; 1 audio cassette
    - Ian Eddy on blacksmithing; Putney, Vermont, 1998-09-15, AFC 2017/001: SR101; 1 audio cassette
    - Lee Webster on quilting; Plymouth, New Hampshire, 1998-09-16, AFC 2017/001: SR102; 1 audio cassette
    - Peter Catchpole on blacksmithing; New Milford, Connecticut, 1998-09-23, AFC 2017/001: SR103; 1 audio cassette
    - Walter Scadden on blacksmithing; Manchester, Connecticut, 1998-09-23, AFC 2017/001: SR104; 1 audio cassette
    - Walter Scadden on blacksmithing; Manchester, Connecticut, 1998-09-23, AFC 2017/001: SR105; 1 audio cassette
    - Toshio Odate on woodworking; Woodbury, Connecticut, 1998-09-23, AFC 2017/001: SR106; 1 audio cassette
    - Toshio Odate on woodworking; Woodbury, Connecticut, 1998-09-24, AFC 2017/001: SR107; 1 audio cassette
    - Craig Burlon, 1998, AFC 2017/001: SR108; 1 audio cassette
    - Charlie Tompkins; Arlington, 2001-08-22, AFC 2017/001: SR109; 1 audio cassette
    - Discussion with crafts people at Campbell Folk School; Brasstown, North Carolina, 2001-10-23, AFC 2017/001: SR110; 1 audio cassette
    - Discussion with crafts people at Campbell Folk School; Brasstown, North Carolina, 2001-10-23, AFC 2017/001: SR111; 1 audio cassette
    - Made in American trip, 2001, AFC 2017/001: SR112; 1 audio cassette
    - Weaver interviews for Spirited Objects, 2001-12-18, AFC 2017/001: SR113; 1 audio cassette
- Series 8: The Potter's Eye and Other Projects, 1970-2008, Bulk: 1995-2007
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Interview Transcript for The Potter's Eye, 2004-2004 (Box-folder 77/6)
    - Writings for book - The Potter's Eye, undated (Box-folder 77/7)
    - Writing drafts - The Potter's Eye, undated (Box-folder 77/8)
    - Writing drafts - The Potter's Eye, undated (Box-folder 78/1)
    - North Carolina Museum of Art exhibit and National Endowment for the Arts grant, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 78/2)
    - The Potter's Eye exhibit notes, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 78/3-4)
    - University of North Carolina seminar - "Art and tradition in North Carolina Pottery", 2005 (Box-folder 78/5)
    - Slide list of North Carolina humanities - The Potter's Eye presentation, 2005 (Box-folder 78/6)
    - Some pots of The Potter's Eye, 2004, 33 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/8)
    - The Potter's Eye exhibit - Japan, 2006 (Box-folder 78/7)
    - Press for The Potter's Eye, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 78/8)
    - Press for The Potter's Eye and exhibition for North Carolina Museum of Art, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 78/9)
    - Printed material re: North Carolina pottery, 1997-2005 (Box-folder 78/10)
    - Newport Folk Festival books, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 78/11)
    - Conference papers, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 78/12)
    - Conference papers, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Various Nancy Sweezy separate works, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 79/2-3)
    - Smithsonian Folklife material, 1971-1991 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - National Council for the Traditional Arts, 1985-1998 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities review, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Consultancies, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 79/8)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 79/9)
    - Participation on panels, 1986-2002 (Box-folder 79/10)
    - American Folklore Society Conference: Louisiana, 1986, 13 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/5)
    - American Folklore Society Conference: New Mexico, 1987, 28 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Boston Harbor, 1991, 17 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Writings - retrospective on 1980's interviews, 2006 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Review by Nancy Sweezy of Our Lives in Our Hands in the Journal of American Folklore, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Smithsonian crafts meeting, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - North Carolina Pottery Center, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Southern Folk Pottery Collectors Society newsletter, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Walkabout with Kate Rinzler, 1995 (Box-folder 80/6)
    - Printed material - Crafts and pottery general, undated (Box-folder 80/7)
    - Four booklets by Philis Alvic, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 89/8)
      Mary Hambidge Weaver of Rabun [1989]; The Weaving Room of Crossnore School, Inc [1998]; Weavers of the Southern Highlands: Berea [1993]; Weavers of the Southern Highlands: The Early Years in Gatlinburg [1991]
    - Ceramic supply material, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 80/8)
    - Southern Folk Pottery Collectors Society auction with Nancy Sweezy piece, 1998 (Box-folder 80/9)
    - Massachusetts Cultural Center advisory panel, 2001 (Box-folder 80/10)
    - Building Creative Economies conference (Ashevulle, North Carolina), 2001-2002 (Box-folder 80/11)
    - Crafts trip and walkabout, 2001 (Box-folder 80/12)
    - Walkabout with Kate: Louisiana Gulf Coast, undated, 73 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Notes regarding interview tapes, 2006 (Box-folder 80/13)
    - Writings - SI Festival talk, 2007 (Box-folder 80/14)
    - NS working folder, 2007 (Box-folder 80/15)
    - Craft in America, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 80/16)
    - Writings - N.H. League, 2007 (Box-folder 80/17)
    - Studio Potter piece, 2001-04-16, afc2017001_cf15; text files; original media: zip disk
    - Interview with Charlie Tompkins, 2001-08-22, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
    - Building Creative Economies - final, 2002, afc2017001_cf15; text files; original media: zip disk
    - NC pottery project, 2006, afc2017001_cf24; text files; original media: CD-ROM
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Country Roads Arlington, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph09_134 to ph09_147 (Box 21-22)
    - NCMA, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph09_148 to ph09_157 (Box 21-22)
    - Unlabeled landscape, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph23_032 to ph23_055 (Box 44)
    - Unlabeled event, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph23_056 to ph23_085 (Box 44)
    - Exhibit Project - North Carolina, 1998, AFC 2017/001: ph24_049 to ph24_051; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - North Carolina to Virginia, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph24_054; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - CYSCA Trip to South Carolina, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph24_055; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Bedford, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_056 to ph24_057; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - New Mexico American Folklore Society, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph24_060 to ph24_063; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - India, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_067 to ph24_079; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - India, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph26_001 to ph26_014; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 47)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - Folk Pottery for a Microwave Generation / SC Folk Ceramics (teaser tape), 2002-06, AFC 2017/001: MV10; 1 videotape
    - Pam Owens and Vernon Owens interview for the book and exhibit, 2004-07-12, AFC 2017/001: SR114; 1 audio cassette
    - Ben Owen interview for book and exhibit, 2004-07-20, AFC 2017/001: SR115; 1 audio cassette
    - David Stuempfle for book and exhibit, 2004-07-21, AFC 2017/001: SR116; 1 audio cassette
    - Kim Ellington, 2004-07-30, AFC 2017/001: SR117; 1 audio cassette
    - Pam Owens and Vernon Owens, 2004-08-15, AFC 2017/001: SR118; 1 audio cassette
    - Kim Ellington no. 2, 2004-08-17, AFC 2017/001: SR119; 1 audio cassette
    - Mark Hewitt, 2004-09-03, AFC 2017/001: SR120; 1 audio cassette
    - Terry Zug at University of North Carolina pottery seminar - "Is a Churn Art?: The Aesthetics of Utilitarian Pottery", 2005-11-04, AFC 2017/001: SR121; 1 audio cassette
    - Charlotte Vestal Brown at University of North Carolina pottery seminar - "Transitions: Seagrove Pottery, Consumers, and the Ascendancy of Craft", 2005-11-05, AFC 2017/001: SR122; 1 audio cassette
    - George Holt and Nancy Sweezy at University of North Carolina pottery seminar - "The Influence of Jugtown on North Carolina Pottery Aesthetics", 2005-11-05, AFC 2017/001: SR123; 1 audio cassette
    - Mark Hewitt at University of North Carolina pottery seminar - "Art and Innovation Within Tradition: Contemporary Ceramics That Echo the Past", 2005-11-05, AFC 2017/001: SR124; 1 audio cassette
    - University of North Carolina pottery seminar - The Potter's Eye panel discussion: Terry Zug, Charlotte Vestal Brown, Nancy Sweezy, Mark Hewitt, George Holt, 2005-11-05, AFC 2017/001: SR125; 1 audio cassette
- Series 9: Personal Files and Correspondence, 1923-2009
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Correspondence - postcards received, 1923 (Box-folder 81/8)
    - Correspondence - Letters sent home by Sweezy while working in Europe for the Office of Strategic Services (OSS), 1944-1946 (Box-folder 81/9)
    - Office of Strategic Services (OSS) European Political Report, 1945 (Box-folder 81/10)
    - Correspondence - letter to mother, 1954 (Box-folder 81/11)
    - Correspondence - Potter Letters, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 81/12)
    - Correspondence - personal, collected postcards from family and friends, 1968-2007 (Box-folder 81/13)
    - Correspondence - personal, 1976-2008 (Box-folder 81/14)
    - Correspondence - personal, 1976-2008, 11 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 82/1-2)
    - Correspondence - George Holt, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 82/3)
    - Collection of personal and family photos, 1971-2005, 18 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 82/4)
    - Family Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 82/5)
    - World travel documents, notes, and printed matter, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 82/6-7)
    - Correspondence and memorials - Ralph Rinzler, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 82/8)
    - Ralph Rinzler memorial Tennessee contact sheets, undated, 22 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/18)
    - Correspondence - Jeffery LaRiche, undated (Box-folder 82/9)
    - Correspondence - Rajeev Sethi, 1998 (Box-folder 82/10)
    - Nancy Sweezy interviewed by David O'Neill, 2009 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Collected papers on folk art and cultural representation, undated (Box-folder 81/2-5)
    - Collected articles by friends and others, undated (Box-folder 81/6)
    - Collected papers regarding crafts, undated (Box-folder 81/7)
    - Guest book from Nancy Sweezy exhibition, 2009 (Box-folder 82/11)
    - Correspondence - professional, 1980-2003, 5 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 83/1-2)
    - Nancy Sweezy personal unsorted papers, undated (Box-folder 83/3-4)
    - Resumes and business cards - Nancy Sweezy, undated (Box-folder 83/5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts National Heritage Fellowship Award to Nancy Sweezy - photos and related material, 2006-2007, 12 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 83/6)
    - Correspondence re: Nancy Sweezy National Endowment for the Arts National Heritage Fellowship Award, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 83/7)
    - Papers collected for memoir, undated (Box-folder 83/8-11)
    - Collected business cards, undated (Box-folder 83/12-13)
    - Collected business cards, undated (Box-folder 84/1)
    - Personal notebooks - Thailand, 1968-1968 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - Personal notebooks - Refugee Arts Group, undated (Box-folder 84/3)
    - Personal notebooks - walkabout, 2001-2001 (Box-folder 84/4)
    - Personal notebooks - Spirited Objects, 2004 (Box-folder 84/5)
    - Personal notebooks - unlabeled, undated (Box-folder 84/6)
    - Personal notebooks - unlabeled, undated (Box-folder 84/7)
    - Calendar books, 1980-1999 (Box-folder 85/1-6)
    - Calendar books, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 86/1)
    - Hanging calendars, 2001-2009 (Box-folder 86/2)
    - Address books, undated (Box-folder 86/3-6)
    - Nancy Sweezy early life, undated, 81 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Nancy Sweezy personal, undated, 73 photographic prints (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Italy, 1994-1994, 66 photographic prints (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Scotland, 1989, 33 photographic prints (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Israel: Galilee, Jerusalem, Aman, Petra, undated, 91 photographic prints (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Blue Ox Mill, California, 1993, 13 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Israel and Kate's party contact sheets, undated, 10 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/15)
    - Smithsonian contact sheet, undated, 1 photographic print (Box-folder 87/17)
    - Contact sheets with corresponding negatives numbers, undated, 5 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/21)
    - Viva Chavez, viva la causa, viva la huelga, 1968, AFC 2017/001: OS5-GR01; 1 color poster, 45 x 30 in.